So, all members of the Global Summit Flotilla have been abducted, not arrested, by Israel.
That's 500 people representing 44 different nations.
44 different nations now have citizens that are in this situation.
These are all members of a humanitarian mission to bring baby formula and toys and food to people that Israel claims they are not starving.
Then, then 30 AIPAC Democrats call on Trump to oppose Palestinian sovereignty, meaning to oppose the right of Palestinians to exist as a people and a country.
Among those are Richie Torres and Wesley Bell, who was paid to go up against Cori Bush and took AIPAC money to get her out of her seat that she rightfully earned as an organizer in St. Louis.
Meanwhile, the remaining plans for Israel are to take the people that they have displaced in Gaza, put them in a camp where they will be given numbers instead of names.
Does this sound familiar to anybody?
And all of them will have their phones confiscated so that they cannot communicate.
This is being reported by Haaretz, which is the Israeli newspaper.
I mean, are you okay with this?
Are you okay with humanitarians being held hostage by a government that you are also held hostage by?
You do understand that the Democrats who are supporting this, they're allowing U.S. citizens like Greg Stoker to be imprisoned.
And you, if you're not calling them into action, are also allowing this.
So when you see me saying, where the f**k is Kamala Harris, it's because I want to know why we don't know if she's doing anything about this.
And yes, she will always be held responsible to hold up the safety of U.S. citizens, just like Bill Clinton did when he went over there to get Lisa Ling's sister out of North Korea.
Yeah, where are Democrats who have taken APAC money and allowed for this to happen?
If they're not out here shouting at the top of their lungs about it stopping, I have a goddamn problem.
And we should be calling them to the mat.
Hakeem Jeffries, Richie Torres, Chuck Schumer, Nancy Pelosi, all of these APAC fiends should be called to the mat.
Yeah, where are they?
Cory Booker, you got all the mouth for 25 hours.
Where are y'all?
Are you behind the scenes?
This behind the scenes madness, I ain't here for it.
Jasmine Crockett, people got all the mouth and they only talk to racists because that's the safest.
Nah, y'all need to be shouting about these Zios.
I said it before and I'll say it again.
These people are deeply bothered.
By a shift in public opinion about them and they watch social media.
So we need to be on here and out there making noise and calling them by name and saying we hold you responsible to make sure they get home safe.
Get that rude, eh?